<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - gr4n173</title>
        <link>http://example.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | gr4n173</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 17:00:49 &#43;0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Nephack 3.0</title>
    <link>http://example.com/nephack3/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 23:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://example.com/nephack3/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction Actually NepHack is one of the Biggest Hacking Competition of Nepal after threatcon which is especially CTF (Jeopardy type) competition which is held annually every year in K.U.( Kathmandu University), Dhulikhel, Nepal. But unfortunately this year due to some internal problem of K.U NepHack 3.0 was held in premises of Cynical Technology .
Event happened at Jan 25–26,2020 but unfortunately I wasn’t able to attend due to my work .]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Scavenger</title>
    <link>http://example.com/scavenger/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://example.com/scavenger/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[HTB:Scavenger Scavenger box was the hardest box after Zetta box. It falls under linux and hard category. Here, everything was all about enumeration, enumeration and enumeration. I&rsquo;ll approach this write-up how I solved it, along with the problems that I had to face during this box. At first I obtained the user flag using whois service and dns zone transfer(axfr) along with ftp by analyzing the .pcap file then used LKM to read root.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Zetta</title>
    <link>http://example.com/zetta/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 20:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://example.com/zetta/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[HTB:Zetta Zetta box was the hardest box till I have done. It falls under linux and hard category. Especially to read the root flag is a quite tough one. I&rsquo;ll approach this write-up how I solved it, along with the problems that I had to face during this box. At first I obtained the user flag using ipv6 and rsync service by uploading my authorized_keys then I used postgres along with logger to read root.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Welcome to my blog</title>
    <link>http://example.com/welcomeblog/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 20:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://example.com/welcomeblog/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Profile is Loading&hellip;&hellip;&hellip;.. ]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Moee-1</title>
    <link>http://example.com/moee-1/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 17:00:49 &#43;0900</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://example.com/moee-1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Details about the first part of <code>Moee</code> Series.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Registry</title>
    <link>http://example.com/registery/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 17:55:28 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://example.com/registery/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><code>Registry</code> box was the hard box. It falls under linux and hard category.Especially to read the root flag was a quite tough one. I’ll approach this write-up how I solved it, along with the problems that I had to face during this box.</p>]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
